const quizData = [
{
    "question": "91. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int a = 18;\nint b = 9;\nint result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);",
    "a": "9",
    "b": "8",
    "c": "7",
    "d": "10",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "92. After the code is executed, what will be the value of `x`?",
    "code": "int x = 48;\nx = x-- - --x + ++x - x++;",
    "a": "48",
    "b": "47",
    "c": "46",
    "d": "49",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "93. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int value = 30;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);",
    "a": "30",
    "b": "29",
    "c": "28",
    "d": "31",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "94. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "int num = 50;\nnum = num-- - ++num + --num - num++;",
    "a": "49",
    "b": "48",
    "c": "51",
    "d": "47",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "95. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "int result = 30;\nresult = result++ - --result + result-- - ++result;",
    "a": "30",
    "b": "29",
    "c": "28",
    "d": "31",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "96. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int x = 26;\nint y = 4;\nint z = x-- - --y + y++ - ++x;\nSystem.out.println(z);",
    "a": "25",
    "b": "26",
    "c": "27",
    "d": "24",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "97. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
    "code": "int counter = 19;\ncounter = counter-- - --counter + ++counter - counter++;",
    "a": "19",
    "b": "18",
    "c": "20",
    "d": "17",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "98. What will be the value of `value` after executing the following code?",
    "code": "int value = 32;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;",
    "a": "32",
    "b": "31",
    "c": "30",
    "d": "33",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "99. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "int num = 52;\nnum = num++ + num-- - --num + ++num;",
    "a": "52",
    "b": "53",
    "c": "54",
    "d": "51",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "100. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int a = 20;\nint b = 10;\nint result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);",
    "a": "10",
    "b": "9",
    "c": "8",
    "d": "11",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "101. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int x = 10;\nint y = 5;\nint z = x-- + --y - y++ - ++x;\nSystem.out.println(z);",
    "a": "9",
    "b": "10",
    "c": "11",
    "d": "8",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "102. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
    "code": "int counter = 15;\ncounter = counter-- + --counter - ++counter - counter--;\n",
    "a": "14",
    "b": "15",
    "c": "16",
    "d": "13",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "103. What will be the value of `value` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "int value = 20;\nvalue = value-- - --value + value++ - ++value;\n",
    "a": "19",
    "b": "20",
    "c": "18",
    "d": "21",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "104. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "int num = 25;\nnum = num++ + num-- - --num + ++num;\n",
    "a": "26",
    "b": "25",
    "c": "24",
    "d": "27",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "105. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int a = 15;\nint b = 8;\nint result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);",
    "a": "5",
    "b": "6",
    "c": "7",
    "d": "4",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "106. After the code is executed, what will be the value of `x`?",
    "code": "int x = 12;\nx = x-- - --x + ++x - x++;\n",
    "a": "11",
    "b": "12",
    "c": "10",
    "d": "13",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "107. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int value = 17;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);",
    "a": "16",
    "b": "17",
    "c": "18",
    "d": "15",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "108. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "int num = 22;\nnum = num-- - ++num + --num - num++;\n",
    "a": "21",
    "b": "22",
    "c": "23",
    "d": "20",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "109. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "int result = 19;\nresult = result++ - --result + result-- - ++result;\n",
    "a": "18",
    "b": "19",
    "c": "17",
    "d": "20",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "110. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int x = 13;\nint y = 6;\nint z = x-- - --y + y++ - ++x;\nSystem.out.println(z);",
    "a": "11",
    "b": "12",
    "c": "13",
    "d": "10",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "111. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
    "code": "int counter = 18;\ncounter = counter-- - --counter + ++counter - counter--;\n",
    "a": "17",
    "b": "18",
    "c": "19",
    "d": "16",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "112. What will be the value of `value` after executing the following code?",
    "code": "int value = 23;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\n",
    "a": "22",
    "b": "23",
    "c": "21",
    "d": "24",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "113. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "int num = 30;\nnum = num++ + num-- - --num + ++num;\n",
    "a": "30",
    "b": "31",
    "c": "29",
    "d": "32",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "114. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int a = 20;\nint b = 9;\nint result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);",
    "a": "10",
    "b": "9",
    "c": "8",
    "d": "11",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "115. After the code is executed, what will be the value of `x`?",
    "code": "int x = 33;\nx = x-- - --x + ++x - x++;\n",
    "a": "32",
    "b": "33",
    "c": "31",
    "d": "34",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "116. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int value = 22;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);",
    "a": "23",
    "b": "22",
    "c": "21",
    "d": "24",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "117. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "int num = 34;\nnum = num-- - ++num + --num - num++;\n",
    "a": "33",
    "b": "34",
    "c": "32",
    "d": "35",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "118. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "int result = 21;\nresult = result++ - --result + result-- - ++result;\n",
    "a": "21",
    "b": "20",
    "c": "19",
    "d": "22",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "119. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "int x = 15;\nint y = 7;\nint z = x-- - --y + y++ - ++x;\nSystem.out.println(z);",
    "a": "14",
    "b": "15",
    "c": "16",
    "d": "13",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "120. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
    "code": "int counter = 20;\ncounter = counter-- - --counter + ++counter - counter--;\n",
    "a": "19",
    "b": "20",
    "c": "21",
    "d": "18",
    "correct": "a"
},
];
    
    


const quiz = document.getElementById('quiz');
const answerEls = document.querySelectorAll('.answer');
const questionEl = document.getElementById('question');
const codeEl = document.getElementById('code');
const a_text = document.getElementById('a_text');
const b_text = document.getElementById('b_text');
const c_text = document.getElementById('c_text');
const d_text = document.getElementById('d_text');
const submitBtn = document.getElementById('submit');

let currentQuiz = 0;
let score = 0;
let selectedAnswers = [];

loadQuiz();

function loadQuiz() {
    deselectAnswers();

    const currentQuizData = quizData[currentQuiz];

    questionEl.innerText = currentQuizData.question;
    codeEl.innerHTML = `<pre><code class="language-java">${currentQuizData.code}</code></pre>`;
    a_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.a;
    b_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.b;
    c_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.c;
    d_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.d;

    hljs.highlightAll(); // Apply syntax highlighting
}

function deselectAnswers() {
    answerEls.forEach(answerEl => answerEl.checked = false);
}

function getSelected() {
    let answer;

    answerEls.forEach(answerEl => {
        if (answerEl.checked) {
            answer = answerEl.id;
        }
    });

    return answer;
}

submitBtn.addEventListener('click', () => {
    const answer = getSelected();

    if (answer) {
        const currentQuizData = quizData[currentQuiz];
        const correctAnswerText = document.getElementById(currentQuizData.correct + "_text").innerText;
        const selectedAnswerText = document.getElementById(answer + "_text").innerText;

        if (answer === currentQuizData.correct) {
            score++;
            alert(`Correct! You selected "${selectedAnswerText}".`);
        } else {
            alert(`Incorrect! You selected "${selectedAnswerText}". The correct answer is "${correctAnswerText}".`);
        }

        selectedAnswers.push({
            question: currentQuizData.question,
            code: currentQuizData.code,
            selected: selectedAnswerText,
            correct: correctAnswerText,
            isCorrect: answer === currentQuizData.correct
        });

        currentQuiz++;

        if (currentQuiz < quizData.length) {
            loadQuiz();
        } else {
            showResults();
        }
    } else {
        alert("Please select an answer!");
    }
});

function showResults() {
    quiz.innerHTML = `
        <h2 style="text-align: center; font-size: 2rem;">Quiz Results</h2>
        <p style="font-size: 1.5rem; text-align: center;">You answered ${score}/${quizData.length} questions correctly</p>
        <div style="margin-top: 2rem; max-height: 400px; overflow-y: auto; padding: 1rem; border: 1px solid #ccc; border-radius: 10px;">
            <h3 style="text-align: center; margin-bottom: 2rem;">Detailed Summary</h3>
            <ul style="list-style-type: none; padding: 0; font-size: 1.2rem;">
                ${selectedAnswers.map((result, index) => `
                    <li style="margin-bottom: 1.5rem;">
                        <strong>Question ${index + 1}:</strong> ${result.question}<br>
                        <pre><code class="language-java">${result.code}</code></pre>
                        <strong>Your Answer:</strong> ${result.selected} (${result.isCorrect ? '<span style="color: green;">Correct</span>' : '<span style="color: red;">Incorrect</span>'})<br>
                        ${!result.isCorrect ? `<strong>Correct Answer:</strong> ${result.correct}` : ''}
                    </li>
                `).join('')}
            </ul>
        </div>
        <div style="text-align: center; margin-top: 2rem;">
            <button onclick="location.reload()" style="font-size: 1.2rem; padding: 0.8rem 1.5rem; background-color: #8e44ad; color: #fff; border: none; cursor: pointer;">Reload Quiz</button>
        </div>
    `;

    hljs.highlightAll(); // Apply syntax highlighting in the summary
}